all right what's up guys welcome back to
another spot so this is my third time
ever doing a podcast with one of my
students here i got the man alec um you
know appreciate you bro yo thanks for
having me on man you know driving down
so i mean um alec kind of stood out in
the discord chat because uh i think what
would you get like two three payouts
from funding companies three pf payouts
now yeah yeah three playoffs yeah so
like i don't know like i mean i try to
be as active as i can within the discord
chat you know like like the best that i
can you know i try to be in there as
active and then one day everybody's just
saying like bro congrats congrats
congrats i'm like bro like what like
what happened bro and then this guy's
out here like flexing yeah it's like my
third payout
company bro so i mean you were telling
me before that you originally came here
from france right because i i want to
get like your backstory because a lot of
people like when they see a successful
trader like yourself you know getting
three payouts from a funding company
like that shows consistency because like
a lot of people like you got to take
into consideration like that means you
pass a challenge you pass a verification
you got to pay out once
twice and then the third time like
there's no like you know like
bullshitting that like like you're
obviously doing something right so
before we get into that i want to know a
little bit more about you and then how
you kind of came into the training
yeah i don't know how far back you want
to go but oh yeah so i mean talk to me
about friends because i've never met
france okay yeah so i pretty much grew
up in france um you know my dad's french
my mom's american
and um i spent the first 15 years of my
life over in france really cool
experience you know it's a way different
culture
you know they appreciate kind of the old
things um you know history and just
really rich culture and like legacy and
all that
and um really cool experience because i
was able to grow up in france you know
looking at the u.s wanting to experience
that as well
and then eventually being able to move
over here i was 15 um
i came over to the us about like maybe
three days before high school started
joining the football team like the day
after i landed and then um
when i was here you know i just did the
whole american experience
but i guess kind of going into this
whole aspect of business and stuff
growing up my dad he kind of ran his own
like business he was in the medical
space and so i grew up with my dad you
know running his own business
having employees and like
having that responsibility of their
livelihoods and growing his own business
and what goes with all that and
that's something that i really wanted to
do myself you know i don't know if it's
like um
you know a problem with authority or
like we wanted to do my own thing but i
was just excited about you know growing
my own
you know legacy and like what i'm able
to produce myself and so kind of growing
up i was always kind of launching my
like business on the side so
you know i had like a car washing thing
and then
getting into college i launched like my
own like moving business
and i kind of ran out with my buddies
and stuff you know like kind of to the
side but i ended up like growing it
pretty well
and then towards the end of college i
started learning a little bit more about
you know entrepreneurship passive income
and i read the book rich dad poor dad
you know it's like everybody's like
starter story right there so that i read
the same book yeah yeah actually like
just kind of showed me the possibility
about you know leveraging your time and
your money
and
i realized that you know
like a moving business was more of like
you know kind of like a self-employed
gig not exactly like a business and so i
needed to kind of create something that
i could you know do that i wouldn't be
physically putting in time to create
income
so i just kind of dove in further i got
my real real estate license
and i kind of started diving into all
that and then i came across a french
company that was like expanding to the
us
and
they initially came to me because they
needed help with like i guess leases for
their
their fitness studios
and then i kind of got to talking with
them i'm like i really love working out
and fitness and all that so and they're
also growing their corporation in the us
so really spoke to me about what they
were doing and working on
so
ended up kind of joining their team i
was like kind of give them different
advice and stuff so they brought me on
and eventually kind of moved up in the
ranks
and that was my main thing for a while
just helping them grow their own
business and stuff and learning a lot
about kind of the corporate side of
things and
recruiting hiring and creating systems
and processes
and then um
i guess if you want to get into the
trading session
how did you come across trading yeah so
um i was pretty much you know working
that job and i was launching a couple
different businesses while i was doing
it and i was doing like affiliate
marketing i tried like wholesaling real
estate um
i did like a couple of different things
a bunch of trial errors yeah yeah really
you know i had the motivation but i
really didn't find like the thing that
really kind of like
inspired me i guess and i really had
that passion for and so i was just kind
of you know diving in further and i
found this like entrepreneur that was
down here in miami you know jeff
seckinger and i just saw his stuff
online he was crushing it
and
i kind of dove into his whole program
and everything and he was talking about
business funding what that was and you
know i was working paycheck to paycheck
you know just like most people i think
it's like sixty percent of americans
live paycheck to paycheck 68 70 yeah
it's huge so i was in the same spot
myself you know i was like trying to
launch my business
but i had this like cap of like capital
and resources and so it's a lot of stuff
i wanted to do but i just didn't really
have like what i needed to scale
and so i dove into his stuff and
i went to one of his
seminars that were down here in miami
and it was like a huge room like
probably like 100 150 people
and
i just like sat down and like randomly
sat down next to this one guy who like
you know i never knew before and we kind
of got to talking and he was like in the
forex space you know i thought forex was
like for like bankers and like
institutions like i traded options
before but like i knew nothing about
forex
and
he was telling me about how he got
funded and he had like all these
accounts and like you've been trading
for like you know about a year and he's
like making a [__] ton of money
and
i kind of dove into his stuff
he ended up kind of showing me some of
the ropes as well like he kind of like
introduced me to baby pips oh yeah calm
yeah
it's really good it's probably like one
of the best educational platforms yeah
it's free
to like get to like get i want to say
like the beginning like any beginners
that hit me up because you know i don't
have a course all i do is yeah yeah okay
like bro like i don't i don't want to
remix baby pips obviously yeah just go
to baby pips you're going to learn the
basics all right the foundations and
then then like that's going to teach you
how to base like it's going to teach you
what a car is like every point of the
car yeah but then you kind of need like
a mentor to teach you how to drive yeah
that's a good example yeah yeah
go ahead and continue that right i mean
pretty much yeah i went through that
whole program learning about like that
the basics really about like you know
even what the charts are and i was
trading options more about like probably
feeling or anything
and uh learn more about like you know
chart patterns and candlesticks with the
yard kind of like the bare basics
and then we kind of started diving a
little bit deeper into like actually how
to trade and so he was more of a swing
trader himself
but i was just kind of starting off man
i was like hungry and so i want to get
this [__] like moving i guess
and so i ended up
you know taking his advice for like kind
of going more the scalping route and so
i tried like really just trial and error
and um every bit of salary i was like
making i was just putting it back into
the
into my my trading and stuff like that
and then
i was doing that for a while
and then i ended up like kind of going
after the the business funding route
getting more funding more capital and
then at the same time i was uh
using that to
do more prop firms i was starting to
dive into youtube and the crazy thing
was that you know i started realizing i
was like wasting a lot of money just
trying these challenges and you know
trying to figure it out
and
i decided like to really take it serious
and like start actually educating myself
and diving into youtube videos and stuff
like that
and it might have been like 10 days
after you know i started diving into
youtube i actually came across your page
you're probably like second or third
person i found for forex on youtube
and like 10 days after i started like
actually wanted to educate myself like
you talked started talking about your
mentorship
so it was kind of wild to me it felt
like you know almost like meant to be
and so um
i dove into your mentorship and man that
[__] like just opened my eyes honestly
um
i really wasn't like going about it with
like a real strategy i guess you know i
was kind of like same thing i was doing
it off the feeling
and um you actually started showing us
more about like you know the structure
of the market and the entries
being patient i think that was really
the main thing for me is being patient
waiting for the trades to come to you
instead of forcing it
and
now you know it's definitely different
pretty much living off my forex earnings
now that's crazy yeah so i mean so take
taking it back a little bit so you said
that originally you had a bunch of
different businesses that you tried kind
of like failed right like i mean not
failed but it just kind of wasn't what
you expected to be so the moving didn't
go down um the other company you're
working with the french company didn't
go down so then you weren't profitable
before the boot camp like you were kind
of like just like getting into it then
you got the bootcamp and then you became
profitable yeah 100 i mean again i was
just like wasting money like trying to
pass these challenges and a lot of the
time i was trying to force it too i was
i started trading gold
and one of my buddies he was trading
gold and you know he seemed like
somewhat successful but
i kind of again like tried getting like
forceful for it and
i'd be like driving and trading like 30
lots on goal trying to pass the
challenge like stupid [__] yeah yeah and
um
and then yeah i came across your program
and actually like learned about
i guess
how to really treat this like a business
kind of how you talk about
all right so that is alec my top student
from my last 30 day bootcamp that i did
two months ago he's received over 50 000
payouts from funding companies and i'm
going to be doing my last boot camp of
this year on september 7th but this boot
camp is very different because i'm gonna
personally be funding one trader that
joins this next boot camp ten thousand
dollars or two traders five thousand
dollars each so you guys can trade and
make money back this is my form of
giving back to those students that don't
only invest in me but invest in
themselves so if you guys want to join
the application list for this last
bootcamp that i'm going to be doing on
september 7th make sure to click the
link below and i'm only going to be
accepting 20 people and there's going to
be one lucky one or 10 000 or 2 winners
of 5 000 each so you guys can go and
trade so make sure you click the link
below so you guys join the application
list
how you talk about yeah i mean something
that i do like to like you know teach
the guys out there i mean first of all
what i like doing with the boot camp
since it's live like it's literally like
live 30 days like you can't really fake
the education at that point because i'm
literally teaching you and like remember
when we first started i'm like bro in
these next 30 days price is going to go
from here to here and then you see it
play out through the whole 30 days so
like that that to me is like the
ultimate like flex i mean like profits
are cool but like if you could predict
something's going to go from here to
here in a certain amount of time that to
me is like the ultimate knowledge when
it comes to training um but i feel like
a lot of people also kind of like how
you were saying they just want to like
pass these challenges too fast they want
to get funded too fast and like we were
doing a real earlier for uh for level up
and then like one of the reals was
basically setting realistic expectations
like if all you have for your knowledge
is just baby pips and all you have is
like a couple youtube videos like don't
expect to make all of these profits
don't expect to pass any challenges
don't expect to have any real results
without any real education a real
foundation so i mean like other than
that like other than the boot camp what
was something that like set aside your
trading completely other than the
education
i mean honestly being able to talk to
you directly about you know what i
thought about the markets being able to
look at it together i thought that was
really interesting because you know
sometimes if you want to go about it
like maybe youtube
and see how it's supposed to look but
then maybe you're just going about it
completely differently and i feel like
sometimes we're looking at the structure
and
the risk management side of things you
know at first i wasn't even really
probably going in the right direction
yeah being able to talk to you that was
huge yeah so what was like one of the
biggest mistakes you were making other
than and like like was it risk
management or was it like risk
management 100
it's so overlooked it's like something
so simple like you showed us the uh like
the
fx book like calculator yeah that like
that itself changed my life that's it
that website yeah and uh because now
like i'll look at my charts and actually
plug in my my tp my stop loss
and i'll actually plug in how much money
i'm risking whereas before you know i
it looks like i'm making enough money
right now or starting to hurt maybe i
should pull out
and that's literally how i was trading
before but now actually being able to
structure my trading and plan it out
beforehand that was huge that was huge
what are your payouts because i know you
have some payoffs like what it like yeah
yeah i mean my first payout was insane
i mean um i passed my challenge i got
the
the log in on like uh like a wednesday
or something
i put in like two trades like the very
next day
and they both hit
and the payout was like 15k fire i got
the literally got the credentials and
within 24 hours i made 15k oh wow yeah
did you continue to trade or you just
stopped trading stopped so you started i
knew like i've
psychologically needed like that first
payout so like no i could do this that's
that's crazy that that you could handle
your emotions like that because a lot of
people they'll see 15k and they'll be
like i want 25. yeah i want 30. so the
fact that you would be able to like to
control yourself and you know hold back
tonight yeah i stopped yeah i wanted
that first payout to know like this is
possible like what was your second
payoff oh 11k
then the last one was like eight a.k.a
okay dope yeah and then do you uh have
like an approach like oh i want to reach
this certain amount of target or it just
kind of just happens
um i really like i'm trying to shoot for
you know probably
one and a half percent a week kind of
thing like you know mostly probably four
percent a month that's kind of my
ultimate goal but as soon as i cross
like maybe like 8k profits i just kind
of pull out
i just kind of cash out and then i just
try to start over honestly because
people don't understand like what what
you could do with four percent on you
were saying like four hundred thousand
dollar account yeah you can make some
damage bro no that's that's awesome i
mean the whole proffer model was like
what attracted me so much to this is
that you know
if you pay 1200 bucks
you pass you get access to 200k i mean
you can't really see this finance
anywhere else honestly
yeah and then what do you do now like on
your free time like what do you do yeah
because that's like the big thing with
your strategy is that you have so much
free time honestly i got like kind of
bored doing this stuff for a while
so um now that i'm doing like the
trading i'm like trying to be you know
diligent with my my strategy
i had like a lot of free time and so i
wanted to put it to use i like being
productive honestly i don't really like
just sitting around and
you know i'll kick it sometimes but i
like actually like building something
and
being productive and so
back when i was able to do the whole
business funding and i got access to you
know over 200k at zero percent interest
and so i thought that was a skill that
was pretty pretty useful
and so i ended up launching a coaching
business that teaches people how to
optimize their personal credit started
llc
use that to then build credit and then
pursue business funding so i hope people
acquire
zero percent interest business funding
so that they can either launch their
business or scale or even invest that's
pretty dope yeah yeah so basically
trading gave you like a gateway to make
like another source of income that's
yeah that's pretty for sure yeah i mean
i use all those
all that like you know income to then
put into marketing like hire another
coach for like learning how to like
advertise myself i guess
and then
put into my softwares and all that so
and then what would you recommend
somebody out there like kind of you
where you were let's say like six months
ago seven months ago like what would you
recommend them to do
it's like the biggest thing is just like
have a game plan honestly like you know
some like when a lot of stuff's just
like kind of like hitting sideways you
know you might feel lost
and um you know just
not really sure what to do
for me like the biggest thing was you
know i was
running the different like businesses
and i tried getting these pap like these
prop firms and all that and
i wasn't really getting
the traction that i was looking for
but once i create like an actual game
plan of like steps and like how i can
actually get to where i want to go and
the first thing i did was actually try
to create like a vision like a plan of
you know what's the end goal
so you know the end goal was i wanted
two funded accounts and i wanted to have
a business that i could actually grow
and then work on
and so
so you're there now bro now yeah yeah so
what's next yeah i mean next is uh
probably my goal really is by the end of
the year i want to get a million dollars
funded
and then my coaching business i want to
grow it to you know be like a
seven-figure business right yeah and
then now that you basically like
have
your your main goals which would be your
trading accounts and then your coaching
other than that that obviously your new
goals that you have set are you like
like are you the type to like buy stuff
with your money or do you like enjoy
life i saw like when you did the
testimonial video for me yeah i'll pop
it over here like the testimonial video
that he did for me where you were at the
keys you're just like living life just
like kicking it in the water so like are
you the type of person to cause like
this is something interesting like i
personally myself like we haven't really
traveled a lot lately but like we like
doing more fun stuff like within the
city um that i do want to travel maybe
starting next year i still think like
i'm young like i just want to stay local
like get to know miami as much as i can
um i have a buddy of mines named sensei
and this guy goes and he travels all of
latin america for like two months yeah
he'll come back for like a week so like
what kind of lifestyle do you like like
to do it i mean honestly i feel like
i've hit my initial goals but i don't
think i'm really where i want to be just
yet so right now i i just reinvest
everything honestly you know
i'm either reinvesting into my business
education advertising what it may be but
i do used to like that fun though so
yeah the main thing for me is i like to
travel you know i i do buy like nice
things here and there but mostly it's
like about experiences for me so you
know i'm going to martinique actually
where where it's like in the caribbean
like the east coast you know about it
yeah hell yeah what is it what is it
it's like this beautiful island it's
like tropical it's got like a volcano oh
it's got a bunch of really nice beaches
and i'm going there for like two months
so that's the kind of stuff that i like
to do just like the experiences and do
something different i like rent a you
know charter boat with my buddies
sometimes
and stuff like that but i feel like i
wouldn't i want to really hit a point
where i'm creating like a lot of passive
income first before i can start to buy
you know like toys and stuff like that
okay talking about your buddies that you
you know hang out with the buddies what
did your buddies or your family like
think of you when you were like starting
this whole training or do they know do
they not know like how did that how did
that go down i really it's my family i
didn't really talk about it too much
when i was starting um you know
my dad as i mentioned he's running his
own business and stuff but i guess he
still
wanted me to be more conservative i
guess in my approach so
the whole time that i was just kind of
guided in the direction of just becoming
a banker
they pay well play it safe and go that
route but again i always had this like
itch of like wanting to do my own thing
and i just didn't really see myself
working like a job my whole life and so
i wasn't that direction so when i was
like working that corporate job with the
fitness company ended up just
quitting
and just taking the leap because i was
making pretty some money but i just knew
that that wasn't really fulfilling me
for what i wanted to do and that wasn't
aligned with my goals
and so i ended up just quitting and then
like the next time i went home which was
probably like you know six weeks maybe
two months later i just kind of broke it
to them and they were all just like kind
of scratching their head like sure
but i ended up doing that i mean family
wise you know they're really supportive
now you know to see like what's been
happening and
you know i think they really just wanted
it more for the aspect of
you know
protection and being able to to know
that i'm gonna be like okay and like
not be homeless i guess yeah and um
so that was the main reason i think for
that but now that they know that you
know i can actually live and take care
of myself i think that's been easier for
them
but then for the buddies wise i mean you
know i have certain buddies that are
actually passionate about this
entrepreneurial stuff too and so we've
definitely grown closer through like the
trial and errors and actually starting
to grow stuff now
and i think that's pretty cool yeah
that's that's something that's funny
that you said about your parents my
parents were you know basically think
the same thing uh when i got q on the
podcast he said it perfectly he was like
like he said like i understand parents
like i like as a parent you don't want
your kid to like you know do something
crazy that you have no idea what's the
outcome going to be that you don't want
to like fall face plant on the floor
that's why you're going to be
conservative and tell them not to do it
um but like i feel like you know as like
parents boys like i have some boys that
have talked to me about some businesses
and i'm like bro that that makes no
sense yeah and then it works and i'm
like bro you know like good for you so i
do understand that point like my like
with me i i completely like isolated
myself from my other friends and i just
focused on myself so the fact that you
did get buddies and like you guys are on
the entrepreneurship right now that is
that is pretty dope yeah i think your
circle is so important honestly it's
like you know the five people you
surround yourself with you're usually
the average of that and so
you know nothing against
the nine to five lifestyle you know if
you want to just live a life in which
you can actually enjoy the weekends you
can kick back after 5 p.m or whatever
and
you're happy in that life that's great
but
for me i was trying to build these
businesses and take the risk that comes
with like entrepreneurship and all that
and so
i need to surround myself with people
that also have that same mindset because
really
you know it's most people aren't aren't
like this they're not just wired to want
to take these risks and be willing to go
to zero that's what it takes to then go
to the next level and so
i think finding that circle is really
important no i i definitely agree like
i've had boys that i tried to put on and
bro it's just not it like they're just
not yeah like they're they're they're
just not willing to put in the same
hours as as i am yeah and then they are
they're okay with their like they're
literally okay with where they are yeah
yeah they're probably happier than where
i am right yeah with the things that
i've achieved so i do agree with you i
do think it is a mindset thing and like
people like that i personally think
you're never going to change that's just
who they're going to be with the way
they're going to be and yeah you know
like you said like i don't i don't you
know downplay them yeah i don't like if
that's what you want you know by all
means yeah if it makes you happy that's
great honestly i mean i just for me like
what makes me happy is knowing that i'm
making this progress so if i'm like you
know up working at 10 11 or even on the
weekends but i'm like coming out with
like this new content or this new video
or this new
idea for my business like that gets me
like really excited honestly so that's
what drives me forward
so then you said that you found me on on
youtube like how did that go so i want
to get like a live testimony from you
right now yeah
how was the boot camp for you bro cause
i have another one that i'm gonna do
maybe in like two weeks so like
how yeah this is what was the last time
the last one that i did was like two
three months ago yeah yeah so like like
what was like your honest experience
like in the bootcamp this isn't like i'm
not paying this guy like he's really
just like about to say yeah no honestly
the the boot camp is what gave me the
structure to be able to actually become
like a per like i'd say live on forex
trading the boot camp teaches you how to
actually approach this as a business
and because forex you actually need to
be serious with this it's not some kind
of side hustle if you want it to be this
needs to be something that you're
actually focused on if you want to
actually make money with for me the
mentorship allowed me to learn about the
different structures of the market
learn about risk tolerance and the whole
psychology i think psychology is
probably maybe one of the biggest
factors of trading
and alex was able to guide us through
the different processes involving how
the market reacts and moves and then how
to anticipate all that stuff so
definitely recommend the mentorship
that's what allowed me to stop wasting
money on all the different challenges
and actually start to make income from
this right here that's crazy but we
gotta get you on level up bro we gotta
yeah
for sure so we have like a certificate
like behind you they can probably see it
like we need we need your name
[Laughter]
so i mean um what would you say like one
piece of advice when it comes to like a
forex trader that is in like the
struggles like just strictly psychology
other than risk management i know you
mentioned risk mana earlier but like
more like technical wise like what was
the thing that just shifted it for you
in the technical analysis i feel like
for me was just like actually having a
strategy honestly before as i mentioned
i was just working more on what looked
like the marquee was doing you know
maybe i saw a big engulfing candle it
looked like it was ready to blow and
then
the very next one just engulfed the
previous candle and i was screwed so
i would say actually having a structure
and sticking to it
because for me i was
trying to scalp and then maybe i would
explore with the swing trading
and need to figure out exactly what
strategy are you looking to pursue
and then being able to
to prepare yourself to spend the time
that might take that to actually master
that strategy as well because i think
there's probably a lot of ways
that you can approach forex trading and
actually be good at it but it'll take
time to actually get to that spot so so
how do you approach it now like what's
your approach to the markets like do you
get on the mornings are you london like
how do you how do you come to the
markets um usually i'll kind of start
the day i'll check out the charts so
i'll start monday mornings i'll like
erase all my charts and remove
everything
and then i'll go back and start to to
create my
my trends i guess so i'll go to the
month weekday four hour and i'll i'll
draw out exactly what's bullish bearish
i'll start there then i'll start to
create the actual levels of interest
that i'm looking for i'll start to draw
out the lines the zones and then i just
start to put in my alerts
and so monday morning i've probably
looked at you know i don't really care i
just kind of look at like 20 different
pairs and i'm looking at 20 different 4x
pairs
and i set up my alerts and then i just
let it go so then i wait for the trace
actually come to me then i'll usually
maybe check it in the evenings in the
mornings but most of the time i'm just
kind of you know working or hanging out
then i'll get an alert
then that lets me know that i actually
need to start looking at the charts
again because we're just talking about
it earlier like the more i tend to look
at the charts the worse i do because i
start to overthink stuff and i try to
force trades and that's when my trading
actually goes down so if i just set up
my alerts and let all the trades come to
me that's when i actually performed the
best so yeah and that's that's that's
funny you say that because a lot of
people see like that i trade like i
don't trade like we don't trade 20 pairs
like yeah we actively watch them yeah
and then whenever it gets to those areas
we trade them exactly but like we're not
like are they like looking at because
like i feel like a lot of people they
come to the markets with like the
scalper mentality they come into the
markets where like oh uh i need to trade
every single day i'm gonna because
people come into the mentality with a
job like they're working a nine to five
so they come to the charts thinking
they're gonna work on nine to five in
the charts but like bro there's just
days where the market's not going to
give you anything yeah so they think
that it's like oh i go work one job i
need one pair and i master this one pair
i'm going to master this one job i'm
going to get paid the most because i
master this one skill set that's just
not how it is like this is like like the
strategy that that like you know that is
taught is you trade based off of how
many confluence and the highest
probability trade sure so you just trade
it's the same strategy across all of the
pairs and the fact that you said that
you can
do that on mondays and then you just
simply get away from the charts bro like
you have set yourself with a mindset
that is like bulletproof like the
markets are not [__] with you man
like yeah like like you're really like
done for it in a good sense meaning that
you're not you're not there on the
charts to make those mistakes when
they're to be made because you're simply
waiting for them to come to your area of
interest yeah i feel like i'm like
trading with the market instead of like
almost against it at that point so
waiting for everything to come to me is
like actually waiting for the market to
kind of do its thing
yeah what's the longest you've had to
trade for
um
probably like a week i guess maybe 10
days or so yeah yeah i like how was that
like how was that like for you it just
feels like wait forever i guess
but at the end of the day it's like with
if that's what you have to do like you
know i'm like ready to do that most of
my trades probably last you know two
three days so yeah sometimes i'll get
lucky a trade just rips in my direction
yeah but most of the time i'm waiting a
couple days for my trades yeah and then
do you still go through like any like
psychological you know like emotions or
just because you seem like a super like
chill guy you seem like just like
nonchalant you know yeah that's probably
my advantage i guess for this whole
thing yeah
but sometimes you know yeah i'll try to
force it i guess you know maybe
if i have a couple of bad trades in a
row i might find myself looking at the
charts more than trying to find like you
know
some trades that might not even be there
and that's definitely happened probably
last three months
but then coming back i tried to you know
if i'm having like a couple bad trades
in a row
and it's even like wednesday or tuesday
even maybe i'll just stop for the week
i'll just stop for the week i'll try to
you know get myself away from it because
i know that if i keep going into this
it's only going to get worse so yeah you
definitely have a very mature trading
mindset because like people like like
there's people that that question me
when i say that and i'm like well like
if it's not working you just yeah yeah
doing it like like it like it shouldn't
be a trick question or you shouldn't
have um
like it's like like a second side to
like wherever it's not doing good you
just come back next week so i do find
that very interesting i like what you
said during the mentorship too in which
you were saying how whenever you take a
trade you act as if you have an investor
right over your shoulder that's asking
you why you're taking this trade so for
me you know if i'm taking this trade i
need to know that i have all the trends
in my direction how the confluences
we're bouncing off a zone and hopefully
even the ema
and that's why i'm taking this because i
have the risk reward that looks good and
i'm not just going in because you know
it looks fun or something yeah just yeah
just because you want to feel involved
yeah exactly yeah i like brother there's
just some random analogies in the boot
camp that i just think about yeah man
like these are fires that's actually
what sticks with you too because you
have that like connection this is
relatable like people people think that
this is chinese or it's something that
you can't relate to like it's very
similar to a lot of things just it's
something new and people are not
familiar with it but it has the same
characteristics as any other business or
as learning any other skill set people
just want to complicate it more because
like you know the
the like how fast you can make a lot of
money right did you have like those
thoughts everywhere i'm like bro like i
need the million today or like you just
cause like i don't think you're like
that you're like a chill guy i mean i
used to kind of be like that i guess
like you know i was
i was first starting entrepreneurship
maybe you know a couple years ago and
i saw people online i guess sometimes
you just try to compare yourself i guess
and stuff like that and i saw these
people making a whole lot of money and
so at first i think i tried making
aggressive moves i would like invest
probably more money than i should have
into different investments that were
like way riskier
and
you know i lost pretty much everything
like on all those different investments
and so at that point
i realized that
there is a risk reward for everything
you do really not even just for trading
but like investments business decisions
and being able to approach it that way
definitely change things and i think
that you know losing on those
investments early on also showed me that
you need to be able to approach things
with that outlook that you know even if
it's your buddy that's offering this to
you or you know it looks good on paper
like there's really nothing promised in
life you need to be able to really
acknowledge that
there's a reward there but there's also
a risk involved yeah
oh that that yeah yeah i feel like you
definitely have a different mindset a
lot of people come into this business
either needing the money needing to pay
some bills
or just chasing it because like it's
just it's there like you can really make
like 100k in a day you know you're
seeing raul right now he's getting crazy
you saw james you turn it to like
20k to like two mil like yes that
possibility is there
but just because that possibility is
there doesn't mean that it's meant for
you just yet right that you could do it
just yet like it's possible but it's
it's not like
it's not qualified for it right same
thing as let's say like you can go to
the gym and you see somebody else
benching you gotta call it 500 pounds
like that doesn't mean that you could do
it like a
taking steroids like he is or like are
you doing everything those ideas
probably not right like you gotta build
up so that's something that it's very
simple and energy and like people just
don't want to look at it like that
because it's very accessible like to
make money in the markets it's very that
you just go with the policy money kick
somebody who's always attempting yeah
it's so tempting
it's it's like it's almost like
like a game people trying to treat it
like
if you click the right buttons then you
jackpot this is not how it works so like
i i try my best to you know try to
explain and educate it as a business uh
yeah i think like trading really is just
like everything else in which you need
to spend the time to actually learn and
master it everyone's gone through this
process of
trying to learn this new skill and
that's what really trading is it's a
skill
and you need to go through that process
of actually being able to learn the
trials and tribulations that might go
through it spend the time on education i
mean just like you mentioned the guys
mentioned maybe 500 like one day he was
leaving that cheese tomorrow yeah you
know he actually had to understand how
to grip the thing and go down and do the
right motion so
that's what you have to do with trading
you have to actually understand the
different structures how the market
moves
being willing to you know maybe even
risk some money to
then acquire that skill set that maybe
one day you can live off of this right
here yeah
well i i love it i love it well i
appreciate you man i hope this keeps
getting more payouts hope to come over
to level up and make some money sure
except for it i appreciate you bro i
hope you know great success appreciate
it appreciate you guys uh make sure to
like comment and subscribe and i'll see
you guys in the next episode